{"data":[{"question":"Were you able to contact John? \" Yes, and he ___ me of a good place to eat here.\"","a":"said","b":"suggested","c":"recommended","d":"told","answer":"4","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something \n- Suggest\/ recommend + Clause","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I think I understand his point. \" Then ___.\"","a":"explain me it","b":"explain it to me","c":"explain it for me","d":"explain for me it","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Explain something to somebody","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"How does she manage it? \" She asks ___ \"","a":"to the students for help","b":"the students for help","c":"for help to the students","d":"to students for help","answer":"2","explain":"\n - Ask sbd for sth: to make a request for help, advice, information","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Even if no violation of law is discovered, it ___ troubling questions of political ethics.","a":"rises","b":"raises","c":"has risen","d":"arises","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Raise: to begin to talk or write about a subject that you want to be considered or a question that you think should be answered","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Eva laid her glasses on the desk and ___ in a chair beside her sister.","a":"seated down","b":"seated herself","c":"set down","d":"sit herself down","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple past tense \n- Seat yourself (in\/on\/beside etc something): to sit down somewhere","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"You look very tired. \" I had to ___ all the dishes after dinner.\"","a":"make","b":"settle","c":"get","d":"do","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We use the verb 'do' when someone performs an action, activity or task: do a crossword, do the ironing ,do the laundry, do the washing, do the washing up...","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"It's time to leave. \" Yes, the clock ___ two o'clock.\"","a":"says","b":"indicates","c":"tells","d":"marks","answer":"1","explain":"\n- We often use \"say\" with \"clock\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Do I have to ___ trains at the next station? \"Yes, you will see the train for London.\"","a":"change","b":"get off","c":"depart","d":"take","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Change trains\/buses\/planes etc: to get off one train, bus, or aircraft and into another in order to continue your journey","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"What happened ? \" As you know, my schoolmates never ___ their clothes well.\"","a":"hanging","b":"hanged","c":"hung","d":"hang","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple past tense \n- Hang - hung - hung","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"How can we settle the problem? \"Well, we must ___ it to her own judgement.\"","a":"believe","b":"express","c":"leave","d":"depend","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Leave: to let something remain in a particular state, position, or condition","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}